Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records Documenting Swimming
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records documenting swimming, 1905-2013; Accession 2013-A-039
  - Organization files
    - Men's Team
      - Photographs, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 918)
      - Pamphlets and brochures, 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 919)
      - Pamphlets and brochures, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 920)
      - Varsity swimming records-information sheets and pamphlets, 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 921)
      - Photographs, 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 922)
      - Pamphlets, statistics and team standings, 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 923)
      - Varsity swimming scores, 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 924)
      - Freshman swimming-information sheets, 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 925)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 926)
      - EISL championships, 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 927)
      - Photographs, 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 928)
      - Photographs, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 929)
      - Pamphlets, scores and statistics, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 930)
      - Varsity swimming-information sheets, statistics and pamphlets, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 931)
      - Rosters and statistics, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 932)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 933-934)
      - Photographs, 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 935)
      - Pamphlets, brochures and newsletters, 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 936)
      - Statistics, information sheets and reports, 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 937)
      - Pamphlets, statistics and reports, 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 938)
      - Rosters and event statistics, 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 939)
      - Swimming & Diving: The Official Coaching Book of the ESSA, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 940)
      - Pamphlets and brochures, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 941)
      - Varsity swimming-statistics and pamphlets, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 942)
      - Freshman swimming-pamphlets and statistics, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 943)
      - Olympic and conference championship statistics and reports, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 944-945)
      - Photographs, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 946)
      - Pamphlets, brochures and newspaper clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 947)
      - Varsity swimming-statistics and reports, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 948)
      - Freshman swimming-statistics, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 949)
      - Photographs, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 950)
      - Varsity swimming-statistics, 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 951)
      - Varsity swimming-pamphlets, 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 952)
      - Freshman swimming-statistics, 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 953)
      - Photographs, 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 954)
      - Photographs, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 955)
      - Championship pamphlets, EISL pamphlets and Brochures, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 956)
      - Varsity swimming-statistics and pamphlets, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 957)
      - Freshman swimming-statistics, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 958)
      - Statistics, reports, pamphlets and rosters, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 959-960)
      - Pamphlets and event summaries, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 961)
      - Varsity swimming-photographs, pamphlets, summaries and statistics, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 962)
      - Freshman swimming-statistics, rosters and newspaper clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 963)
      - Statistics, event summaries, pamphlets and information sheets, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 964)
      - Statistics, event summaries and information sheets, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 965)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and statistics, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 966)
      - Pamphlets, statistics and event summaries, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 967)
      - Statistics, event summaries and newspaper clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 968)
      - Freshman swimming-statistics and rosters, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 969)
      - Pamphlets, rosters, statistics and photographs, 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 970)
      - Varsity swimming-rosters, statistics and pamphlets, 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 971)
      - Freshman swimming-rosters, statistics and newspaper clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 972)
      - Pamphlets and photographs, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 973)
      - Yale Olympic swimmers, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 974)
      - Swimming Carnival, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 975)
      - Freshman swimming-rosters and statistics, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 976)
      - Varsity swimming-rosters and statistics, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 977)
      - Pamphlets, statistics, rosters and summaries, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 978-979)
      - Pamphlets, statistics and reports, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 980)
      - Photographs, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 981)
      - Pamphlets, statistics and newspaper clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 982)
      - Pamphlets, photographs and correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 983)
      - Photographs, schedule of events, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 984)
      - Eastern Swimming Championships, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 985-986)
      - Pamphlets, photographs, statistics and summaries, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 987)
      - Pamphlets, photographs and statistics, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 988)
      - Photographs and pamphlets, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 989)
      - Photographs and pamphlets, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 990)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and scores, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 991)
      - Photographs, pamphlets, correspondence and scores, 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 992)
      - Pamphlets, photographs and results, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 993)
      - Photographs and pamphlets, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 994)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and newspaper clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 995)
      - Photographs, pamphlets, correspondence and statistics, 1982-1983 (Box 40, Folder 996)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and statistics, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 997)
      - Photographs, pamphlets, correspondence and results, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 998)
      - Photographs, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 999)
      - Photographs, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 1000)
      - Photographs, pamphlets, statistics and rosters, 1985-1986 (Box 41, Folder 1001)
      - Pamphlets, photographs, statistics, correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 1002)
      - Pamphlets, photographs and summary, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 1003)
      - Photographs and pamphlets, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 1004)
      - Photographs, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 1005)
      - Pamphlets, statistics and newspaper clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 1006)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 1007)
      - Pamphlets, statistics and rosters, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 1008)
      - Pamphlets, statistics and team book, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 1009)
      - Photographs, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 1010)
      - Pamphlets and photographs, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 1011)
      - Rosters, statistics and team book, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 1012)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 1013)
      - Pamphlets and photographs, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1014)
      - Pamphlets, statistics, team book and newspaper clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1015)
      - Statistics, results and rosters, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1016)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1017)
      - Photographs, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 1018)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and awards, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 1019)
      - Statistics, results and summaries, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 1020)
      - Newspaper and newsletter clippings, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 1021)
      - Photographs and pamphlets, 1994-1995 (Box 43, Folder 1022)
      - Newsletters, statistics and rosters, 1994-1995 (Box 43, Folder 1023)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 43, Folder 1024)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and awards, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 1025)
      - Newsletters, statistics and rosters, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 1026)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 1027)
      - Photographs, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 1028)
      - Improve Your Swimming, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 1029)
      - Results, correspondence and event schedule, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 1030)
      - Statistics, newsletters and rosters, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 1031)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 1032)
      - Newsletters and photographs, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 1033)
      - Statistics, rosters, pamphlets and brochures, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 1034)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 1035)
      - Pamphlets and photographs, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 1036)
      - Statistics, rosters and event schedules, 1998-1999 (Box 44, Folder 1037)
      - Pamphlets, brochures and programs, 1998-1999 (Box 44, Folder 1038)
      - Photographs, 1998-1999 (Box 44, Folder 1039)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1998-1999 (Box 44, Folder 1040)
      - Pamphlets, programs and correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 45, Folder 1041)
      - Photographs and pamphlets, 1999-2000 (Box 45, Folder 1042)
      - Statistics, rosters and event schedules, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 1043)
      - Statistics, pamphlets, rosters and event schedules, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 1044)
      - Newspaper clippings, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 1045)
      - Pamphlets and photographs, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 1046)
      - Newspaper clippings, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 1047)
      - Results, statistics, rosters and event schedules, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 1048)
      - Newsletters, results, statistics, event schedules, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 1049)
      - Photographs, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 1050)
      - Photographs, newsletters, pamphlets, 2001-2002 (Box 46, Folder 1051)
      - Schedule of events and team book, 2001-2002 (Box 46, Folder 1052)
      - Photographs, 2001-2002 (Box 46, Folder 1053)
      - Photographs and pamphlets, 2002-2003 (Box 46, Folder 1054)
      - Photographs, team book and rosters, 2003-2004 (Box 46, Folder 1055)
      - Photographs, team book and programs, 2004-2005 (Box 46, Folder 1056)
      - Statistics, rosters and schedules, 2004-2005 (Box 46, Folder 1057-1058)
      - Newsletters and photographs, 2005-2006 (Box 46, Folder 1059)
      - Statistics, rosters and event schedules, 2005-2006 (Box 46, Folder 1060)
      - Correspondence and newspaper clippings, 2005-2006 (Box 46, Folder 1061)
      - Swim team results, 2006-2007 (Box 47, Folder 1062)
      - Photographs, team book and newsletter, 2006-2007 (Box 47, Folder 1063)
      - Schedules of events and newspaper clippings, 2007-2008 (Box 47, Folder 1064)
      - Correspondence and article, Alex Righi, 2007-2008 (Box 47, Folder 1065)
      - Photographs, team book and programs, 2007-2008 (Box 47, Folder 1066)
      - Photographs, team book and programs, 2008-2009 (Box 47, Folder 1067)
      - Photographs, newsletters and statistics, 2009-2010 (Box 47, Folder 1068)
      - Photographs, 2010-2011 (Box 47, Folder 1069)
      - Photographs, 2011-2012 (Box 47, Folder 1070)
    - Women's Team
      - Action shots, 1977-1983 (Box 48, Folder 1071)
      - Team photo descriptions, 1973-1992 (Box 48, Folder 1072)
      - Rosters and photographs, 1971-1972 (Box 48, Folder 1073)
      - Correspondence and photographs, 1972-1973 (Box 48, Folder 1074)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and rosters, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 1075)
      - Photographs, pamphlets, rosters and statistics, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 1076)
      - Photographs, rosters and statistics, 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 1077)
      - Pamphlets, rosters, statistics and photographs, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 1078)
      - Pamphlets, rosters and statistics, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 1079)
      - Photographs, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 1080)
      - Pamphlets, rosters and statistics, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 1081)
      - Statistics, rosters and summaries, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 1082)
      - Photographs, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 1083)
      - Pamphlets, rosters, statistics and summaries, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 1084)
      - Pamphlets, schedules and event summaries, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 1085)
      - Pamphlets, correspondence and statistics, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 1086)
      - Photographs, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 1087)
      - Pamphlets, rosters, statistics and photographs, 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 1088)
      - Pamphlets, rosters and statistics, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 1089)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and statistics, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 1090)
      - Pamphlets, photographs, summaries and statistics, 1982-1983 (Box 50, Folder 1091)
      - Photographs, rosters and pamphlets, 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 1092)
      - Photographs, statistics, rosters and pamphlets, 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 1093)
      - Photographs, pamphlets, rosters and statistics, 1985-1986 (Box 51, Folder 1094)
      - Statistics, rosters and pamphlets, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 1095)
      - Photographs, statistics, results and pamphlets, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 1096)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and statistics, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 1097)
      - Photographs, statistics, rosters and event pamphlets, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 1098)
      - Photographs, rosters, statistics and summaries, 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 1099)
      - Photographs, statistics, summaries and pamphlets, 1991-1992 (Box 51, Folder 1100)
      - Photographs, newspaper clippings, statistics and rosters, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 1101)
      - Statistics, photographs, results, pamphlets and newspaper clippings, 1993-1994 (Box 52, Folder 1102)
      - Statistics, summaries, photographs and newspaper clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 52, Folder 1103)
      - Photographs, event summaries, statistics and rosters, 1994-1995 (Box 52, Folder 1104)
      - Newspaper clippings, statistics, rosters and photographs, 1995-1996 (Box 52, Folder 1105)
      - Photographs, newspaper clippings, statistics, summaries and pamphlets, 1996-1997 (Box 52, Folder 1106)
      - Pamphlets, schedules, photographs and statistics, 1997-1998 (Box 52, Folder 1107)
      - Photographs, statistics, event schedules and pamphlets, 1998-1999 (Box 52, Folder 1108)
      - Pamphlets, photographs and statistics, 1999-2000 (Box 53, Folder 1109)
      - Pamphlets, photographs and newspaper clippings, 2000-2001 (Box 53, Folder 1110)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and event programs, 2001-2002 (Box 53, Folder 1111)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and event programs, 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 1112)
      - Pamphlets, photographs and event schedules, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 1113)
      - Pamphlets, photographs and event programs, 2004-2005 (Box 53, Folder 1114)
      - Statistics, pamphlets and photographs, 2005-2006 (Box 53, Folder 1115)
      - Photographs, pamphlets, correspondence and summaries, 2006-2007 (Box 53, Folder 1116)
      - Photographs and correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 53, Folder 1117)
      - Team book, event program, pamphlets, schedules and photographs, 2008-2009 (Box 53, Folder 1118)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and schedules, 2009-2010 (Box 53, Folder 1119)
  - Restricted files
    The Restricted files series consists of records removed from the Athlete files and Organizational files series that contain any medical and/or academic information on swim team athletes and sensitive team correspondence. The files are restricted until January 1, 2086.
    - Athlete Files-Men
    - Athlete Files-Women
    - Men's Team- Correspondence, Undated (Box 59, Folder 1557)
- Photographs documenting the Yale Swim Team, 1986-2013; Accession 2014-A-028
  - Individual photographs-men and women, 2011-2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Folder contains photographs of Caroline Bank, Zurez Khan, Ege Gurdeniz, James Remigino, Leslie Robinson, and Elise Sowah
  - Team photographs-men, 1986-2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Team photographs-men and women, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Team photographs-women, 1987-2008 (Box 1, Folder 4)